export const data = [
  { "id": 1, "unit": 0, "chapter": 0, "topic": "test topic", "question": "test answer", "answer": "test answer", "graph": "test graph" },
  { "id": 2, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "leading coefficient and degree", "question": "What is the degree and the leading coefficient of this polynomial: 10*x**4 + 9*x**3 - 7*x**2 + 9*x + 7", "answer": "The degree of this function is the highest exponent in the polynomial, 4. \n    Therefore the leading coefficent is the coefficent of the term that is degree 4, 10", "graph": null },
  { "id": 3, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "leading coefficient and degree", "question": "What is the degree and the leading coefficient of this polynomial: 5*x**2 - 5*x + 1", "answer": "The degree of this function is the highest exponent in the polynomial, 2. \n    Therefore the leading coefficent is the coefficent of the term that is degree 2, 5", "graph": null },
  { "id": 4, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "leading coefficient and degree of polynomial function", "question": "What is the degree and the leading coefficient of this polynomial: 10 x^{3} + 4 x + 10", "answer": "The degree of this function is the highest exponent in the polynomial which is 3. \n    Therefore the leading coefficent is the coefficent of the term that is degree 3 which is 10", "graph": null },
  { "id": 5, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "end behaviour", "question": "\"What is the end behaviour of this function x - 8", "answer": "Find where f(x) approaches when x->∞ and x ->-∞. Answer: Q2->Q2", "graph": null },
  { "id": 6, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "end behaviour", "question": "\"What is the end behaviour of this function 5 x^{4} - 7 x^{3} + 4 x^{2} - x - 8", "answer": "Find where f(x) approaches when x->∞ and x ->-∞. Answer: Q1->Q2", "graph": null },
  { "id": 7, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "end behaviour", "question": "\"What is the end behaviour of this function - 2 x", "answer": "Find where f(x) approaches when x->∞ and x ->-∞. Answer: Q2->Q2", "graph": null },
  { "id": 8, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "end behaviour", "question": "\"What is the end behaviour of this function - 10 x^{6} - 3 x^{5} - 3 x^{4} - 7 x^{3} + 10 x^{2} + 8 x + 2?", "answer": "Find where f(x) approaches when x->∞ and x ->-∞. Answer: Q1->Q2", "graph": null },
  { "id": 9, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "end behaviour", "question": "\"What is the end behaviour of this function 8 x^{2} + 2 x + 4?", "answer": "Find where f(x) approaches when x->∞ and x ->-∞. Answer: Q2->Q1", "graph": null },
  { "id": 10, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "end behaviour", "question": "\"What is the end behaviour of this function 7 x + 9?", "answer": "Find where f(x) approaches when x->∞ and x ->-∞. Answer: Q2->Q4", "graph": null },
  { "id": 11, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "end behaviour", "question": "\"What is the end behaviour of this function - 2 x^{4} + 8 x^{3} - 2 x^{2} - 3 x - 8?", "answer": "Find where f(x) approaches when x->∞ and x ->-∞. Answer: Q1->Q2", "graph": null },
  { "id": 12, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "end behaviour", "question": "\"What is the end behaviour of this function 9 x^{3} + 8 x^{2} - 7 x + 10?", "answer": "Find where f(x) approaches when x->∞ and x ->-∞. Answer: Q2->Q4", "graph": null },
  { "id": 13, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "end behaviour", "question": "\"What is the end behaviour of this function 4 x^{2} + 8 x - 1?", "answer": "Find where f(x) approaches when x->∞ and x ->-∞. Answer: Q2->Q1", "graph": null },
  { "id": 14, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "end behaviour", "question": "\"What is the end behaviour of this function 9 x + 6?", "answer": "Find where f(x) approaches when x->∞ and x ->-∞. Answer: Q4->Q2", "graph": null },
  { "id": 15, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "end behaviour", "question": "\"What is the end behaviour of this function - 2 x^{6} - 3 x^{5} + 2 x^{4} + x^{3} + 5 x^{2} - 2 x + 6?", "answer": "Find where f(x) approaches when x->∞ and x ->-∞. Answer: Q1->Q2 or For Q1 -> Q2: as x approaches positive infinity, y approaches positive infinity and as x approaches negative infinity, y approaches positive infinity", "graph": null },
  { "id": 16, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "end behaviour", "question": "\"What is the end behaviour of this function 5 x - 9?", "answer": "Find where f(x) approaches when x->∞ and x ->-∞. Answer: For Q2 -> Q4: as x approaches negative infinity, y approaches positive infinity and as x approaches positive infinity, y approaches negative infinity.", "graph": null },
  { "id": 17, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "odd or even", "question": "Show that the following function is even, odd or neither: - 8 x^{4} - 6 x^{2} + 2 x + 4", "answer": "The function is neither even nor odd: $f(x) = - 8 x^{4} - 6 x^{2} + 2 x + 4$, because $f(-x) = -f(x)$ algebraically simplifies to $- 8 x^{4} - 6 x^{2} - 2 x + 4 \\neq - 8 x^{4} - 6 x^{2} + 2 x + 4$", "graph": null },
  { "id": 18, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "interval notation", "question": "Convert this inequality into interval notation: X >= 2", "answer": "X ∈ [2, +∞)", "graph": null },
  { "id": 19, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "interval notation", "question": "Convert this inequality into interval notation: 0 <= X <= 28", "answer": "X ∈ [0, 28]", "graph": null },
  { "id": 20, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "interval notation", "question": "Convert this inequality into interval notation: 4  <  X  <  13", "answer": "X ∈ (4, 13)", "graph": null },
  { "id": 21, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "interval notation", "question": "Convert this inequality into interval notation: -32  <  X  < = 39", "answer": "X ∈ (-32, 39]", "graph": null },
  { "id": 22, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "interval notation", "question": "Convert this inequality into interval notation: X <= 18", "answer": "X ∈ (-∞, 18]", "graph": null },
  { "id": 23, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "interval notation", "question": "Convert this inequality into interval notation: -14 \\geq X", "answer": "X ∈ (-∞, -14]", "graph": null },
  { "id": 24, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "interval notation", "question": "Convert this inequality into interval notation: -40 \\leq X \\leq 36", "answer": "X ∈ [-40, 36]", "graph": null },
  { "id": 25, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "interval notation", "question": "Convert this inequality into interval notation: 40 \\geq X > -6", "answer": "X ∈ [40, -6)", "graph": null },
  { "id": 26, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "what is a function", "question": null, "answer": "No this fails the vertical line test.", "graph": "\\mathtt{\\text{x = 2 * y**2 + 10 * y + 4 + -9 * y**3 + -8 * y**2 + -4 * y}}" },
  { "id": 27, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "what is a function", "question": "Is this a function: 3 x^{3} + 7 x^{2} - 10 x + 4", "answer": "Yes this passes the vertical line test.", "graph": "3 x^{3} + 7 x^{2} - 10 x + 4" },
  { "id": 28, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "what is a function", "question": "Is this a function: \\mathtt{\\text{x = 9 * y**2 + -5 * y + 5 + -3 * y**3 + -6 * y**2 + -4 * y}}", "answer": "No this fails the vertical line test.", "graph": "\\mathtt{\\text{x = 9 * y**2 + -5 * y + 5 + -3 * y**3 + -6 * y**2 + -4 * y}}" },
  { "id": 29, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "what is a function", "question": "Is this a function: 4 x^{4} + 7 x^{3} - 4 x^{2} - 10 x - 7", "answer": "Yes this passes the vertical line test.", "graph": "4 x^{4} + 7 x^{3} - 4 x^{2} - 10 x - 7" },
  { "id": 30, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "what is a function", "question": "Is this a function: 3 x^{3} - 4 x^{2} - 4 x - 1", "answer": "Yes this passes the vertical line test.", "graph": "3 x^{3} - 4 x^{2} - 4 x - 1" },
  { "id": 31, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "what is a function", "question": "Is this a function: 7 x^{4} + x^{3} - 3 x^{2} - 6 x + 6", "answer": "Yes this passes the vertical line test.", "graph": "7 x^{4} + x^{3} - 3 x^{2} - 6 x + 6" },
  { "id": 32, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "what is a function", "question": "Is this a function: 6 y^{3} + 11 y^{2} + 5 y - 5", "answer": "No this fails the vertical line test.", "graph": "6 y^{3} + 11 y^{2} + 5 y - 5" },
  { "id": 33, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "what is a function", "question": "Is this a function: - 9 x^{4} - 6 x^{3} + 10 x^{2} - 10 x + 4", "answer": "Yes this passes the vertical line test.", "graph": "- 9 x^{4} - 6 x^{3} + 10 x^{2} - 10 x + 4" },
  { "id": 34, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "what is a function", "question": "Is this a function: - 4 y^{3} - y^{2} - 4 y + 2", "answer": "No this fails the vertical line test.", "graph": "- 4 y^{3} - y^{2} - 4 y + 2" },
  { "id": 35, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "what is a function", "question": "Is this a function: 2 x^{2} + 8 x - 8", "answer": "Yes this passes the vertical line test.", "graph": "2 x^{2} + 8 x - 8" },
  { "id": 36, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "is this relation a function?", "question": "Determine if the following relation is a fucntion: {(100, 75), (-5, 87), (-57, -99), (-5, 12), (-5, -20), (-90, -27)}", "answer": "No it is not a function as there are multiple Xs that are the same, failing the vertical line test.", "graph": null },
  { "id": 37, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "factoring", "question": "Factor: 7 x^{2} + 14 x + 56", "answer": "7 \\left(x^{2} + 2 x + 8\\right)", "graph": null },
  { "id": 38, "unit": 1, "chapter": 1, "topic": "factoring", "question": "Factor: 9 x^{2} + 54 x + 27", "answer": "9 \\left(x^{2} + 6 x + 3\\right)", "graph": null },
  { "id": 39, "unit": 1, "chapter": 0, "topic": "solving quadratic equations", "question": "Solve: 4 x^{2} + 2 x + 6 = 6", "answer": "Answer: x ∈ \\left[ - \\frac{1}{2}, \\  0\\right]", "graph": null },
  { "id": 40, "unit": 1, "chapter": 0, "topic": "solving quadratic equations", "question": "Solve: 4 x^{2} + 7 x + 8 = 10", "answer": "Answer: x ∈ \\left[ -2, \\  \\frac{1}{4}\\right]", "graph": null },
  { "id": 41, "unit": 0, "chapter": 0, "topic": "domain and range of functions", "question": "What is the domain and range of this fucntion: 19 \\left(- 17 x - 221\\right)^{2} - 190", "answer": "Domain: x ∈ ℝ Range: y ∈ [-190, ∞)", "graph": null },
  { "id": 42, "unit": 0, "chapter": 0, "topic": "domain and range of functions", "question": "What is the domain and range of this fucntion: - 17 \\left(119 - 7 x\\right)^{2} - 238", "answer": "Domain: x ∈ ℝ Range: y ∈ (-∞, -238]", "graph": null },
  { "id": 43, "unit": 0, "chapter": null, "topic": "finite differences", "question": "Given these points, determine if the function is linear, quadractic or neither. ", "answer": "It is linear. The first are the same. ", "graph": "(-7, -1902.0), (-6, -1175.0), (-5, -660.00), (-4, -321.00), (-3, -122.00), (-2, -27.000), (-1, 0E-124), (0, -5.0000), (1, -6.0000), (2, 33.000), (3, 148.00), (4, 375.00), (5, 750.00), (6, 1309.0), (7, 2088.0)" },
  { "id": 44, "unit": 0, "chapter": null, "topic": "finite differences", "question": "Given these points, determine if the function is linear, quadractic or neither. ", "answer": "It is linear. The first are the same. ", "graph": "(-7, -809.00), (-6, -489.00), (-5, -267.00), (-4, -125.00), (-3, -45.000), (-2, -9.0000), (-1, 1.0000), (0, 3.0000), (1, 15.000), (2, 55.000), (3, 141.00), (4, 291.00), (5, 523.00), (6, 855.00), (7, 1305.0)" },
  { "id": 45, "unit": 1, "chapter": 2, "topic": "constant differences", "question": "\"What is the leading coefficient and the sign of this polynomial given the table? ", "answer": "To find the leading coefficient, find the constant difference and divide it by the factorial of the degree. \n    The constant difference is ([[-110.00, -82.000, -58.000, -38.000, -22.000, -10.000, -2.0000, 2.0000, 2.0000, -2.0000, -10.000, -22.000, -38.000, -58.000, -82.000], [28.000, 24.000, 20.000, 16.000, 12.000, 8.0000, 4.0000, 0, -4.0000, -8.0000, -12.000, -16.000, -20.000, -24.000], [-4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000]], -4.0000). ([[-110.00, -82.000, -58.000, -38.000, -22.000, -10.000, -2.0000, 2.0000, 2.0000, -2.0000, -10.000, -22.000, -38.000, -58.000, -82.000], [28.000, 24.000, 20.000, 16.000, 12.000, 8.0000, 4.0000, 0, -4.0000, -8.0000, -12.000, -16.000, -20.000, -24.000], [-4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000, -4.0000]], -4.0000)/2! = -2. Sign is +. ", "graph": "(-7, -110.00), (-6, -82.000), (-5, -58.000), (-4, -38.000), (-3, -22.000), (-2, -10.000), (-1, -2.0000), (0, 2.0000), (1, 2.0000), (2, -2.0000), (3, -10.000), (4, -22.000), (5, -38.000), (6, -58.000), (7, -82.000)" },
  { "id": 46, "unit": 1, "chapter": 2, "topic": "constant differences", "question": "\"What is the leading coefficient and the sign of this polynomial given the table? ", "answer": "To find the leading coefficient, find the constant difference and divide it by the factorial of the degree. \n    The constant difference is -96.000. -96.000/4! = -4. Sign is +. ", "graph": "(-7, -12311), (-6, -6917.0), (-5, -3525.0), (-4, -1565.0), (-3, -563.00), (-2, -141.00), (-1, -17.000), (0, -5.0000), (1, -15.000), (2, -53.000), (3, -221.00), (4, -717.00), (5, -1835.0), (6, -3965.0), (7, -7593.0)" },
  { "id": 47, "unit": 1, "chapter": 2, "topic": "constant differences", "question": "Find which finite difference is constant and its value of this polynomial: - 4 x - 7", "answer": "Since the degree of the polynomial is 1, the 1 differences will be constant. To find the \n    value of the constant difference, multiply the leading coefficient and the factorial of the degree. 1!*-4 = -4", "graph": null },
  { "id": 48, "unit": 1, "chapter": 3, "topic": "equations and graphs of polynomials", "question": "Provide the degree, intercepts of this polynomial and graph: \\left(x - 1\\right) \\left(x + 5\\right)^{2}", "answer": "X-int: -5, 1\n-int: -25 \nTurning Points: 2", "graph": "\\left(x - 1\\right) \\left(x + 5\\right)^{2}" },
  { "id": 49, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: - \\frac{\\left(2 x - 14\\right)^{0.5}}{5} - \\frac{1}{15}", "answer": "Vertically compressed by a factor of 1/5 ,Reflection in x-axis ,Vertical translation 1/3 units upwards ,Horizontally compressed by a factor of 1/2 ,Horizontal translation 7 units to the right", "graph": null },
  { "id": 50, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: - 9 \\left(10 x + \\frac{5}{2}\\right)^{3} - \\frac{36}{5}", "answer": "Vertically stretched by a factor of 9, Reflection in x-axis, Vertical translation 4/5 units upwards, Horizontally compressed by a factor of 1/10, Horziontal translation 1/4 units to the left, a = -9 c = 4/5 d = -1/4 k = 10", "graph": null },
  { "id": 51, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: \\left(x - \\frac{1}{3}\\right)^{2} + 10", "answer": "Vertical translation 10 units upwards, Horizontal translation 1/3 units to the right, a = 1 c = 10 d = 1/3 k = 1", "graph": null },
  { "id": 52, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: \\frac{\\left(4 x - 28\\right)^{2}}{3} - \\frac{2}{3}", "answer": "Vertically compressed by a factor of 1/3, Vertical translation of 2 units downwards, Horizontally compressed by a factor of 1/4, Horizontal translation 7 units to the right, a = 1/3 c = -2 d = 7 k = 4", "graph": null },
  { "id": 53, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: -72 - \\frac{9}{x - 8}", "answer": "Vertically stretched by a factor of 9, Reflection in x-axis, Vertical translation 8 units upwards, Horizontal translation 8 units to the right, a = -9 c = 8 d = 8 k = 1", "graph": null },
  { "id": 54, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "equations and graphs of polynomials", "question": "Provide the intercepts of this polynomial and graph: 9 \\left(x + 1\\right)^{2} \\left(x + 2\\right)", "answer": "X-int: -2, -1\ny-int: 18 \nTurning Points: 2", "graph": "9 \\left(x + 1\\right)^{2} \\left(x + 2\\right)" },
  { "id": 55, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: - \\frac{4}{5} - \\frac{1}{5 \\cdot \\left(45 - 5 x\\right)}", "answer": "Vertically compressed by a factor of 1/5, Reflection in x-axis, Vertical translation 4 units upwards, Horizontally compressed by a factor of 1/5, Reflection in y-axis, Horizontal translation 9 units to the right, a = -1/5 c = 4 d = 9 k = -5", "graph": null },
  { "id": 56, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: - 8 \\left(x + 2\\right)^{3} - 56", "answer": "Vertically stretched by a factor of 8, Reflection in x-axis, Vertical translation 7 units upwards, Horziontal translation 2 units to the left, a = -8 c = 7 d = -2 k = 1", "graph": null },
  { "id": 57, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: 45 - 9 \\left(\\frac{x}{3} - 3\\right)^{3}", "answer": "Vertically stretched by a factor of 9, Reflection in x-axis, Vertical translation of 5 units downwards, Horizontally stretched by a factor of 1/1/3, Horizontal translation 9 units to the right, a = -9 c = -5 d = 9 k = 1/3", "graph": null },
  { "id": 58, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: \\left(7 x + 35\\right)^{3} + 10", "answer": "Vertical translation 10 units upwards, Horizontally compressed by a factor of 1/7, Horziontal translation 5 units to the left, a = 1 c = 10 d = -5 k = 7", "graph": null },
  { "id": 59, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: 100 - 10 \\left(6 x - \\frac{24}{5}\\right)^{3}", "answer": "Vertically stretched by a factor of 10, Reflection in x-axis, Vertical translation of 10 units downwards, Horizontally compressed by a factor of 1/6, Horizontal translation 4/5 units to the right, a = -10 c = -10 d = 4/5 k = 6", "graph": null },
  { "id": 60, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: 16 - 2 \\left(- \\frac{ x }{ 2} - \\frac{ 1}{ 4}\\right)^ { 2}", "answer": "Vertically stretched by a factor of 2, Reflection in x - axis, Vertical translation of 8 units downwards, Horizontally stretched by a factor of 1 / 1 / 2, Reflection in y - axis, Horziontal translation 1 / 2 units to the left, a = -2 c = -8 d = -1 / 2 k = -1 / 2", "graph": null },
  { "id": 61, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: 5 \\left(9 x - 54\\right)^{0.5} - 45", "answer": "Vertically stretched by a factor of 5, Vertical translation of 9 units downwards, Horizontally compressed by a factor of 1/9, Horizontal translation 6 units to the right, a = 5 c = -9 d = 6 k = 9", "graph": null },
  { "id": 62, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Given the transformations of this parent function x^{2}, write the transformed equation for this function: Vertically stretched by a factor of 2, Vertical translation of 3 units downwards, Horizontally stretched by a factor of 1/1/5, Horziontal translation 8 units to the left", "answer": "y = 2 \\left(\\frac{x}{5} + \\frac{8}{5}\\right)^{2} - 6", "graph": null },
  { "id": 63, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "polynomial properties", "question": "Write an polynomial based on the descriptions: Degree: 4, Double root at x = 7, Double root at x = -4, Start quadrant: 2 End quadrant: 1 ", "answer": "Equation: a \\left(x - 7\\right)^{2} \\left(x + 4\\right)^{2} where a > 0", "graph": null },
  { "id": 64, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "transformations of polynomials", "question": "Describe the transformations of the following function and find values of a, k, c, d: - 3 \\left(6 x + 42\\right)^{2} - \\frac{12}{5}", "answer": "Vertically stretched by a factor of 3, Reflection in x-axis, Vertical translation 4/5 units upwards, Horizontally compressed by a factor of 1/6, Horziontal translation 7 units to the left, a = -3 c = 4/5 d = -7 k = 6", "graph": null },
  { "id": 65, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "characteristics of polynomials from equation", "question": "Find the least possible degree, sign of the coefficent, x-intercepts, and the intervals of this function: - 5 \\left(x - 8\\right) \\left(x - 3\\right)^{3}", "answer": "x_intercepts, y_intercept, degree, leading_coefficient, intervals_positive, intervals_negative", "graph": "- 5 \\left(x - 8\\right) \\left(x - 3\\right)^{3}" },
  { "id": 66, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "characteristics of polynomials from equation", "question": "Find the least possible degree, sign of the coefficent, x-intercepts, and the intervals of this function: \\left(x - 8\\right)^{2} \\left(x + 10\\right)^{3}", "answer": "x_intercepts: -10, 8, y_intercept: 64000, degree: 5, leading_coefficient 1, intervals_positive \\left(-10, 8\\right) \\cup \\left(8, \\infty\\right), intervals_negative \\left(-\\infty, -10\\right)", "graph": "\\left(x - 8\\right)^{2} \\left(x + 10\\right)^{3}" },
  { "id": 67, "unit": 1, "chapter": 4, "topic": "characteristics of polynomials from graph", "question": "Find the least possible degree, x-intercepts, and the intervals of this function based on the graph", "answer": "x_intercepts: -1, 2, 3, y_intercept: 288, degree: 6, leading coefficient: 8, intervals positive: \\left(-\\infty, -1\\right) \\cup \\left(-1, 2\\right) \\cup \\left(2, 3\\right) \\cup \\left(3, \\infty\\right), intervals negative: \\emptyset", "graph": "8 \\left(x - 3\\right)^{2} \\left(x - 2\\right)^{2} \\left(x + 1\\right)^{2}" },
  { "id": 68, "unit": 1, "chapter": 3, "topic": "finding polynomial equation from graph", "question": "Write an polynomial equation based on the graph shown: ", "answer": "To write the polynomial equation based on the graph, first find the roots of the function and write the possible equation in factored form. Then find the y-intercept or some other point, sub it in and solve for the leading coefficent a. \n    In factored form, the potential polynomial equation is a \\left(x - 3\\right)^{2} \\left(x - 2\\right)^{3}, where a is the leading coefficent. The y-intercept is 864/83. Plug in (0, 864/83) into the factored form and solve for a which is [-12/83]. Therefore, the equation \n    of this polynomial function is -12*(x - 3)**2*(x - 2)**3/83.", "graph": "- \\frac{12 \\left(x - 3\\right)^{2} \\left(x - 2\\right)^{3}}{83}" }];
